couponsforzipcodes.com 2010-09-30

# Free Online Coupons Code | Online Discount Promo Coupon Codes | Promotional Coupon Codes | Buy Discount Coupon Codes

### Privacy Policy

Couponsforzipcodes.com respects your right to privacy and anonymity on the web. We created this privacy policy to inform you of the steps we take to protect your personal information, how we use and protect any personal information you choose to share with us by entering our website. This policy may change from time to time, so please check back periodically. This privacy policy applies to the entire [www.couponsforzipcodes.com](http://www.couponsforzipcodes.com/) web site. We assure you that should we ask you to provide us with any personal or identifying information, such information will only be used in a manner specified in this privacy statement. This privacy policy will tell you: 

What information we collect.

How we use information.

Under what circumstances, if any, we disclose the information.

### What information we collect

We collect personally identifiable information about you when you register with us, send us an e-mail or call us, enter a sweepstakes, enrol or participate in an on-line survey. We may collect the following personally identifiable information about you: 

Name

Mailing address

Email address

Phone Number

Demographic profile (like your age, gender, occupation, education and durables owned)

Interests (such as news, sports, travel and so on)

We will never request your password, user name, credit card information or other personal information through e-mail. This practice, called "phishing", is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. 

We will collect certain anonymous information in standard usage logs through our Web server, including computer-identification information obtained from "cookies," sent to your browser from: 

The Web server and stored on your hard drive

The IP address, assigned to the computer which you use

The domain server through which you access our service

The type of computer you're using

The type of web browser you're using

This data is used strictly for the analysis and compilation of statistical traffic reports, trends and improve the performance of our servers. We will not share this data with any outside party. To serve you faster and with better quality, we use "cookies" technology. Cookies are small bits of code, usually stored on a user's computer hard drive, which enable a Web site to "personalize" itself for each user.   
We generally use cookies to reduce the time it takes for pages to load on your computer. 

We may also allow advertisers and other third parties to place cookies onto your computer when you visit this website. The cookies placed by advertisers and other third parties are used to keep track of the web searches you make while visiting this website, as well as your web surfing behaviour on this website and other websites you may visit. That information is used to show you advertisements tailored to your interests on this and other websites, and/or to keep track of your response to each ad. Cookies are not tied to your personal information. 

###  When do we share information 

We do not rent, sell or share your personal information and we will not disclose any of your personally identifiable information to third parties unless: 

We have your permission

To help investigate, prevent or take action regarding unlawful and illegal activities, violations of Couponsforzipcodes.com Terms of Use

Special requests/order from legal authorities or law enforcement agencies requiring such disclosure, court orders

### Option to limit sharing of information

Couponsforzipcodes.com offers a newsletter periodically to its opt-in e-mail subscribers, highlighting hot deals, coupons or promotions at leading online merchants. The newsletter is distributed only to the opt-in subscribers. We will not send or tolerate spam. All opt-in subscribers have an option to unsubscribe from the web site and opt-out from receiving future newsletters. Except as stated above, we will not use our subscriber's e-mail ID in any other way whatsoever.

### Links to other websites

Our website may offer links to other sites. Other sites have their own policies regarding privacy. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such Web sites. If you visit one of these sites, we suggest you to review the privacy policy on that site.

###  Children 

We recognize the particular importance of protecting privacy where children are involved. We are committed to protecting children's privacy on the Internet. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13. 

### Warning about Fraudulent E-mails

We will never request your User name, Password, Credit card information or other Personal information through e-mail. If you receive an e-mail that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do not respond. This policy describes the personal information that we collect from our customers, why we collect it, and how we use it. If you have any questions regarding our privacy policy, you can contact the Company via e-mail at [info@couponsforzipcodes.com](mailto:info@couponsforzipcodes.com)

Couponsforzipcodes.com is the one stop Portal destination for free online Discount coupon codes, Promotional coupon codes, discount coupon codes, Grocery coupons, Travel Offers, Free Shipping, Manufacturer / Store rebates, Bargain / Discount Shopping deals to save money for all online shoppers. We do best bargain hunting for you and We constantly receive and update our site with new Discount coupons from thousand of stores every day. We strive to turn your shopping into a real fun. Please View our Privacy Policy.
